glossybelle.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy – Glossy Belle

At GlossyBelle.com, the privacy of my viewers is very important to me.  In this privacy policy, I will be summarizing the types of personal information that are received, collected, and how they are used on my site.

First and most importantly, I will never share your name, email address, or other personal information to anyone without your direct consent.

### Log Files

Like many other websites, I use log files to assist in gathering broad information to analyze when, where, and how often traffic flows to my site.

These log files include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, platform type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamps, referring/exit pages, and the number of clicks.

None of this information is linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

When you submit a comment on this site, it will store cookies on your computer.  These cookies store your name, email address, and website URL so you don’t have to re-input these fields the next time you leave a comment.  In addition, the WordPress blog platform records your IP address when you submit a comment in order to fight spam.

Viewers may choose to subscribe to email blog updates by submitting an email address to the email subscription form. I reserve the right to communicate with subscribers regarding information related to this site.  Subscribers may choose to unsubscribe anytime after opting-in by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link which is included in every email.

Again, no personal information will be shared with anyone unless direct permission is given. However, if you still wish to disable cookies, you may do so by modifying your Internet browser’s settings.  You can find the instructions to disable them in your browser’s help section.

### Advertisers

I use external advertising companies and networks to display ads as well as web analytical tools to understand how visitors engage on this site.  These third-party ads and web tools may contain cookies and/or use web beacons to collect information.  As these cookies and/or web beacons are collected by these networks and companies themselves, GlossyBelle.com has no control or access over these cookies.

### External Links

This site contains links to external websites.  I am not responsible for the privacy policies of these external websites or any information that may be collected by them.  I recommend that you take a look at their privacy policies, as this privacy policy only applies exclusively to this particular site.

### Children Under 13

GlossyBelle.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If I discover I have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, I will delete that information immediately.  Please contact me if you believe my website has any information from or about anyone under 13.

### Consent

Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this privacy policy.

This policy was last revised on May 25, 2018 and is subject to change without notice at any time.  If you have any questions regarding this disclosure policy, please feel free to [contact me](https://glossybelle.com/contact/).

### Disclosure Policy

You may have noticed there are some affiliate links and sponsored content on this site.  I may receive a small commission if you purchase through those affiliate links and this will _not_  cost you any additional charge or add anything extra to your purchase.  In order to help keep this site alive and running, I accept forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.  I really appreciate it when my readers click on these links because it helps pay the bills!

I may be compensated to provide opinions on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though I receive compensation for these posts or advertisements, I promise to always give my absolute, complete honest opinions, beliefs, or experiences on these topics or products. All views and opinions expressed on this site are purely my own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

Glossybelle.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

This policy was last revised on May 25, 2018 and is subject to change without notice at any time.  If you have any questions regarding this disclosure policy, please feel free to [contact me](https://glossybelle.com/contact/).
